<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string-array name="NormQuotes">
        <item>And he was standing there, reading one of those big books. \n\nYou know the kind. Usually you can’t even understand their stupid titles, and when you try to read them you get one word in and get really sleepy. \n\nAnd it’s so stupid to try anyway, because if the stupid book is any good they’ll make a TV movie out of it and then you can watch that instead</item>
        <item>And you’d correct him, but the thing is, you’re not sure you remember it a hundred percent accurately yourself. \n\nIt turns out your memory isn’t the precise court stenographer you think it is, getting every word down just so. \n\nIt’s more like the sketch artist way at the back of the courtroom who is doing his level best to capture images that no longer are.</item>
        <item>As Adolf Hitler once said, all publicity is good publicity.</item>
        <item>Before I was famous I had a whole bunch of jobs where all I needed was boots. \n\nPeople would look right past me, or if they did look at me, it was with a mean look. \n\nBut when I got famous, people would look at me and smile and wonder where they knew me from. \n\nIf they flat-out recognized me, they\'d laugh and dance like they\'d won a prize, and I\'d just stand there and smile and feel warmth from their love. So the fame made the world, which is a real cold place, a little less cold.</item>
        <item>Death is a funny thing. \n\nNot funny haha, like a Woody Allen movie, but funny strange, like a Woody Allen marriage.</item>
        <item>Earlier this week, Marlon Brando met with Jewish leaders to apologize for comments he made on Larry King Live, among them that "Hollywood is run by Jews". \n\nThe Jewish leaders accepted the actor’s apology and announced that Brando is now free to work again.</item>
        <item>I hate when people say \"touché\" after you say something funny. \n\nI don’t know what it means, but I know that I hate it.</item>
        <item>I\'ll admit that I\'m deeply closeted, but I\'ll never admit that I\'m gay.</item>
        <item>Long after I left the segment, the term "fake news" became the ordinary way to describe what was done on SNL as well as The Daily Show and The Colbert Report. \n\nSo who’s the idiot now?</item>
        <item>Now that all hope is gone, a deep relief has taken its place, and I allow myself to enjoy it before the despair sets in.</item>
        <item>On the final night, Adam Sandler told me the following season would be a rough, divisive one, and he wanted to know which side I’d take. \n\nI told him I wanted to be on the side of the guy who had shoved the baby tomatoes up his ass. Adam smiled.</item>
        <item>She said she could no longer live in New York, that she was being tormented day and night by some obsessive stalker. \n\nThis caught me completely by surprise, as I had taken to hanging around Sarah’s apartment, hiding in the bushes day and night, watching her come and go, and I had never seen any signs of a stalker.</item>
        <item>Sometimes a writer\'s strike is good. \n\nMaybe if we had a writer\'s strike now, people would have to read Shakespeare instead of James Patterson.</item>
        <item>The only time having a cult following is a great thing is when you are actually in a cult.</item>
        <item>The plain truth is that Adam Eget is an alcoholic and that’s why he doesn’t drink. \n\nMe, I’m not an alcoholic and that’s why I do drink. \n\nLife sure is funny that way.</item>
        <item>Well, the results are in, and once again Microsoft CEO Bill Gates is the richest man in America. \n\nGates says he is grateful for his huge financial success, but it still makes him sad when he looks around and sees other people with any money whatsoever.</item>
        <item>When I was right beside Ben Matlock, I threw the Archie comic away and grabbed the biggest, thickest book I could find and turned to a random page. \n\nThen I loudly said, "What the fuck? I certainly didn’t see that shit coming.  Ben Matlock turned his back to me.</item>
        <item>Women are attracted to funny men, it is often said. \n\nThis is not true. \n\nIt only appears this way because women laugh at everything a very handsome man says. So this gives the very handsome men the idea that they are funny.</item>
        <item>Compared to politics, I think sports is funnier, because it\'s inconsequential. And politics can be real important and all that. \n\nThe more pointless something is, the funnier it is, you know? And the more grave or important things are… \n\nYou know, some comedians can get this disease where they get serious all the time.</item>
        <item>I always told everybody the perfect joke would be where the setup and punch line were identical.</item>
        <item>I don\'t know the difference between a hippie and a hipster \n\nbut, it\'s fun to watch either one of them get beat up.</item>
        <item>I think clever people think that poor people are stupid.</item>
        <item>Note to self: \n\nno matter how bad life gets, there\'s always beer.</item>
        <item>OJ Simpson was in a different kind of courtroom this week attempting to regain custody of his two children. \n\nIn order to prove to the court how much he loves his kids, OJ pointed out \n\nquote: \'Hey, they\'re still alive, aren\'t they?\'</item>
        <item>Our passions may be compared to certain slaves—\n\nthe more severity we show them, the better they obey us.</item>
        <item>When I hear a guy lost a battle to cancer, that really did bother me, that that\'s a term. \n\nIt implies that he failed and that somebody else that defeated cancer is heroic and courageous.</item>
        <item>I once walked in on my parents having sex. \n\nIt was the most embarrassing thirty minutes of my life.</item>
        <item>You know, with Hitler, the more I learn about that guy, the more I don\'t care for him.</item>
        <item>They\'re like \'\'You\'re an alcoholic.\'\' I go \'\'No, I\'m not.\'\' \n\nAnd then apparently that\'s what alcoholics say too, you know?</item>
        <item>Chess players think checker players are dumb. \n\nBut I love playing checkers. Plus, the red ones are tasty.</item>
        <item>Many people are skeptical about marriage of Michael Jackson and Lisa Marie Presley. \n\nThey say, Lisa Marie is more of a sit-at-home type, while Michael Jackson is more of a homosexual pedophile</item>
        <item>They say that if you\'re afraid of homosexuals, it means that deep down inside you\'re actually a homosexual yourself. \n\nThat worries me because I\'m afraid of dogs</item>
        <item>When Mozart would sit down and compose a new piano concerto, he’d first pause, close his eyes, and say to himself, \n\n\"I better make this as hard as f*ck to play.\"</item>
        <item>You ever lie for no reason at all? Just all of sudden, a big lie spills out of your evil head. \n\nLike a guy will come up to you, "Hey, did you ever see that movie with Meryl Streep and a horse?" And you go, "Yes." \n\nIn the back of your head, you\'re like, "What in the hell am I lying about over here? I stand to gain nothing by this lie."</item>
        <item>I just got back from New York. You ever been there? \n\nThere was a big gay parade going on there when I was there, and I never been to one of them, and I like a parade. I always like a parade. \n\nSo, I go there, and it turns out, it\'s just a bunch of gay guys</item>
        <item>I don’t want fancy things. I don’t want fancy, smancy things. I don’t even want fancy, smancy, wancy things. \n\nWhat I want is to waste your time</item>
        <item>I wouldn\'t call myself a fan of Steampunk. \n\nBut I will say, its the healthiest way to prepare punk.</item>
        <item>I\'m not gay, so I don\'t know much about Broadway musicals</item>
        <item>Man, them engagement rings, boy, they cost a lot. I was looking at \'em. Cost like a thousand bucks, two thousand bucks, y\'know. Three thousand bucks. Something like that, four thousand bucks. \n\nBig number divisible by a thousand, anyways.</item>
        <item>All kinds of violence on the TV. You\'re not supposed to watch violence on the TV. \n\nChildren, they can\'t watch it \'cause they\'re afraid maybe the kids will copy something they see on the TV. \n\nI can\'t even get a funny cartoon anymore because some 12-year-old somewhere watched a particularly violent episode of the Road Runner-Coyote show, and the next day, they found him at the bottom of a canyon, two giant springs strapped to his feet.</item>
        <item>I don’t do much. I’m too lazy. That’s my problem. Hang around my couch, watching the TV. Just too lazy. \n\nI realized this the other day, I get hit my a truck tomorrow - a big truck could hit me - paralyze me from the neck down. \n\nWouldn’t affect my lifestyle a bit really.</item>
        <item>He has the disease of alcoholism. \n\nAnd he came to me and he told me, and I\'m the kind of guy that likes to look at the bright side of things. \n\nSo I told him, I said, "Richie, it\'s true that you have a disease and everything, but I think you got the best one."</item>
        <item>My wife dresses up like a nurse; then, I dress up like a nurse, also. And then, we don\'t even have sex, either. \n\nWe just sit behind this huge, semicircular wooden desk and get annoyed when people buzz us for juice.</item>
        <item>I went to a hypnotist. He put me under a spell, and every time I had a craving for a cigarette, I would throw up. \n\nIt\'s very embarrassing right after sex. \n\nI find it pretty hard to get that second date after that. Girls get all snobby after you barf on them.</item>
        <item>I don’t care for sex. I find it an embarrassing, dull exercise. \n\nI prefer sports, where you can win.</item>
        <item>Sex couldn\'t be simpler. I think there\'s only like five things you can do in the whole f*cking thing. \n\nYou ever think you invented a sixth? \n\nThen later you go, "Ah, in all humility, I guess that was pretty close to number five."</item>
        <item>Comedy is surprises, so if you\'re intending to make somebody laugh and they don’t laugh, that’s funny.</item>
        <item>This is the amount of time you think about sex: every once in a while. \n\nThe problem becomes, when you think about it, it\'s all you can think about. It encompasses your whole brain. \n\nYou\'re like a f*cking werewolf or something. Usually you\'re a civilized human being, but then every couple of days, you\'re like "Arrrgh." Then you\'ve got to close the blinds.</item>
        <item>I quit smoking and nothing much is different. Except I can taste my food. \n\nI went to a friend\'s place for dinner and I was like… \n\nWhat\'s this zingy, zangy thing you\'re serving me here? Never tasted anything so zingy and zangy. \n\n… A boiled potato, eh? Huh.</item>
        <item>A man\'s wife goes into a coma.  The doctor says "There is only one way of reviving your wife but it\'s a little unconventional. \n\nYou go in there and have oral sex with her" \n\nThe man says"my god...." Doctor says "I know I know, but I\'ve seen it work" The man says "OK doc, I\'ll try anything, I\'m desperate" \n\nHe goes into his wifes room, closes the door behind him. He comes out five minutes later and says"Doc, I don\'t think it\'s working....she\'s choking"</item>
        <item>I endorse podiums \n\nThat’s a product I can stand behind!</item>
        <item>They call gambling a disease, but it’s the only disease where you can win a bunch of money.</item>
        <item>I feel bad for the homeless guy, but I feel really bad the homeless guy\'s dog, because he must be thinking \n\n\'Man, this is the longest walk ever"</item>
        <item>The other day I found a baby bird that had fallen out of its nest. \n\nI love animals, and I thought to myself \'I\'m going to get this little guy back to its nest\'. \n\nNow, it took me about 5 or 6 throws…</item>
        <item>The other day I tell my wife, "when I look into the mirror I only see an old fat man, I need you to make me feel better about myself." \n\nShe says "you have perfect eyesight."</item>
        <item>ID is a funny abbreviation. The I stands for I and D strands for dentification.</item>
        <item>What is the last thing you want to hear after blowing Willie Nelson? \n\n\'I\'m not Willie Nelson\'</item>
        <item>When I was a child they told me, "The children are our future." \'Now that I\'m grown, they\'re saying it\'s actually these new children. \n\nI know a Ponzi scheme when I see one.</item>
        <item>I saw a pig, a cow, and a horse. \n\nI told my wife, “Those look like some of your relatives. \n\nShe replied, “Yeah, my in-laws!”</item>
        <item>The city of Las Vegas now has a gigantic ferris wheel that is drawing huge crowds. \n\nAlso drawing thousands to Las Vegas…whores!</item>
        <item>Before I met my wife, I always felt incomplete. \n\nNow I\'m finished.</item>
        <item>I feel the same way about slaves as I do shirts with flame patterns on them. \n\nI don\'t want to be friends with anyone who owns either of them</item>
        <item>Regarding the war on terror… Fighting it in the Middle East seems a little crazy. \n\nI would\'ve started with our nation\'s haunted houses.</item>
        <item>When you\'re single and trying to attract a partner, it\'s important to project the qualities you desire… which I understand, \n\nbut boy-oh-boy have I had to suck a lot of dick lately…</item>
        <item>Yesterday I had a picture framed, \n\nnow it\'s doing time upstate for armed robbery.</item>
        <item>I need to have glasses to see my family. \n\nSpecifically, two glasses… of scotch!</item>
        <item>I saw my little nephew and he asked me "where would be the worst place to get a bug-bite". \n\nI thought about it and said \'Maybe the eye? Where do you think?\' and he said \'Brazil\'.</item>
        <item>I signed up for my company\'s 401k \n\nbut I don\'t think I can run that far.</item>
        <item>If I was grading constellations, my review and description for Orion\'s Belt would be just three stars.</item>
        <item>My girlfriend\'s mad at me right now. \n\nLast night during sex I yelled the name of her ex-boyfriend.</item>
        <item>I know I\'m not the most attractive man in the world, \n\nwhen women look at me I can tell they\'re over-dressing me with their eyes.</item>
        <item>I was raised in a broken home, \n\nmy father was a drunk carpenter.</item>
        <item>I had a wild night last night, \n\nI was in an orgy. It was me, my iPad, my laptop and my TV while my phone watched.</item>
        <item>I\'ve never been on top of the latest trends. \n\nWhen everyone was burning CDs I was still burning books.</item>
        <item>A friend of mine said that his biggest fear is that ISIS or some terrorist group like that will get hold of a dirty bomb and explode it over a major city within the United States and kill tens of millions of people… \n\n…because then the blowback against innocent muslims would be absolutely terrible.</item>
        <item>Crowds in Brazil greeted arriving Olympians with signs reading \'Welcome to Hell\'. \n\nTheir local Chamber of Commerce really needs to brush up on the basics.</item>
        <item>There\'s no hard evidence that flossing helps your teeth much, scientists now say, \n\nthough they add that it is a great activity for people who enjoy tedious repetitious drudgery.</item>
        <item>A heatwave striking in New York has caused horse manure to spontaneously combust, \n\nso for the first time in history you can explain why New York City smells like a flaming pile of horseshit.</item>
        <item>Last week Pope Francis paid a sombre visit to Auschwitz which surprised me because I thought he was one of those fun ghosts.</item>
        <item>The Blue Man Group has been forced by the federal government to hire an orange man and a purple woman.</item>
        <item>A new report by the CDC reports that only one third of Americans use condoms while two thirds are still pretty cool.</item>
        <item>Ever since Trump\'s new immigration policy came in, the band \'Foreigner\' is scared.</item>
        <item>They say curiosity killed the cat but \n\nI don\'t think we should rule out that shifty-lookin\' kid next door…</item>
        <item>Something tells me a \'cock-and-bull story\' has a different meaning at a gay rodeo.</item>
        <item>You know I\'m happy to help out a friend, \n\nbut the next time my roommate asks for help putting on sunscreen, he better be talking about his back. \n\nFool me once!</item>
        <item>You know what\'s not as easy as pie? \n\nBaking an actual fucking pie!</item>
        <item>There\'s no use crying over spilt milk, \n\nunless the milk was spilt on your father\'s fresh corpse right before his funeral.</item>
        <item>When I grew up, my family was so poor we didn\'t have a pot to piss in, so we pissed in other people\'s pots. \n\nWe\'d break into people\'s houses in the dead of night, find people\'s pots and take a giant piss in them because we had accumulated full bladders from holding down urine all day long from waiting to piss in people\'s pots.</item>
        <item>I don\'t want to shoot myself in the foot but my left big toe is a neo-nazi. \n\nEven worse, my big right toe believes that there should be a gender pay gap.</item>
        <item>A group of crows is called a murder, a group of unicorns is called a blessing and a group of cows is called my in-laws!</item>
        <item>A hippo\'s mouth is wide enough to fit a four foot tall child, \n\nunfortunately after measuring the hippo\'s mouth, almost all the children were eaten.</item>
        <item>Look, I know the bible says not to covet thy neighbour\'s wife, \n\nbut it doesn\'t say a damn thing about not coveting thy neighbour\'s husband, especially his sweet hot fuckin\' asshole.</item>
        <item>The Statue of Liberty is setting a bad example for young women. \n\nWhen times get tough, you can\'t just stand motionless for centuries holding a torch.</item>
        <item>Artifacts from Auschwitz are set to go on tour for the first time. \n\nExperts believe this will be Miley Cyrus\' darkest opening act yet.</item>
        <item>A new study finds that men are more likely to blame \'stress from work\' as the contributor to poor mental health \n\nwhile women are more likely to jabber on about something or other.</item>
        <item>They announced there\'s going to be another Twilight movie and the little girl inside me is really excited.</item>
        <item>I made a bad business decision, I started an online business, \n\nyou know what I sold? \n\nBrick &amp; Mortar.</item>
        <item>I may not have book smarts, but you know what I do have? \n\nSupermarket flyer smarts!</item>
        <item>How do you get a tissue to dance? \n\nYou put a little boogie in it.</item>
        <item>Roses are gray, Violets are gray, Tulips are gray, \n\nBecause I\'m a dog.</item>
        <item>Call me old fashioned, but I long for the days when wives stayed at home and only cost three goats.</item>
        <item>I was once trapped on a desert island and to be honest, the five albums I brought didn\'t help a goddamn thing.</item>
        <item>I don\'t want fancy things. Or fancy-shmancy things. I don\'t even want fancy-shmancy-wancy things or fancy-shmancy-take-a-trip-to-Francey things! What I want is wasting your time and mine.</item>
        <item>A lot of people are excited for self-driving cars and so am I. \n\nFinally, I\'ll feel what it\'s like to kill without having any personal responsibility.</item>
        <item>If you can’t handle me when I’m covered in the blood of a boar I’ve just sacrificed to the Gods, \n\nthen you don’t deserve me during the bountiful harvest that will result.</item>
        <item>Male authors are obsessed with female bodies, going on and on about webbed feet and soft insulat- \n\noh I\'m sorry, that\'s male OTTERS.</item>
        <item>I can\'t stand stuck-up bodies of water. \n\nIt\'s like, \'Get over yourself, Lake Superior\'</item>
        <item>Let\'s be honest, most people you see going skinny dipping are actually just going dipping.</item>
        <item>If I could add one president to Mt. Rushmore it would be James Polk, \n\nbecause I\'m interested to know what he looked like.</item>
        <item>I\'ve been jogging for a few months and I recently set a new record for a 5-mile run: \n\n3 miles.</item>
        <item>To me perfect sex is like a carwash: \n\nYou start by lining up right and going in slow and you finish when three Mexican dudes run up and furiously towel you off.</item>
        <item>A storm picked up eggs and milk over the Rockies and is now battering the Midwest.</item>
        <item>Now I ain\'t saying she\'s a gold digger, but she does have several shovels, picks and panning sluices strapped to her burro.</item>
        <item>If you\'re one of those people that complains that CVS receipts are too long, \n\nyou\'re going to fucking hate books.</item>
        <item>Wearing glasses doesn\'t always make you look smarter. \n\nFor example, you must wear them on your face.</item>
        <item>Take everything you know about bread and throw it out the window… \n\nNow, let me tell you about this invention I made: Bread</item>
        <item>Hey, who\'s this graffiti artist who draws chalk outlines of people in the bad parts of town? \n\nI don\'t like \'em!</item>
        <item>If you\'re sitting around with your thumb up your ass, \n\nhow could you possibly think you were doing nothing. It just doesn\'t make sense.</item>
        <item>Prison rapes are delicious. \n\nOh, wait, I\'m sorry, prison crêpes.</item>
        <item>The inside of the human body is more of a miracle than you\'d first think \n\nsince everything goes on in there in total darkness.</item>
        <item>A lot of people stress out about getting crows\' feet, \n\nbut personally I would be more concerned about their long, razor-sharp beaks.</item>
        <item>Boy… how my mom worked all day, cared for me, put food on the table, \n\nand killed all those drifters is really something.</item>
        <item>The most disturbing thing about Disneyland is seeing all those smiling people walking around wearing Mickey Mouse\'s severed scalp.</item>
        <item>When Mozart would sit down to compose a new piano concerto, he would first pause, close his eyes, and say to himself, \n\n"I\'d better make this hard as fuck to play"</item>
        <item>I wonder who\'s buried in the grave of the guy who invented the Ol\' Switcheroo.</item>
        <item>I don\'t fat-shame women because you can\'t judge a book by it\'s cover. \n\nOf course, if it\'s too damn thick, no-one\'s going to read it.</item>
        <item>Bad news for e-cigarette users: \n\nYou look fuckin\' stupid.</item>
        <item>Words cannot describe your beauty, Adam Eget. \n\nBut numbers can. You\'re a 4.</item>
        <item>A bird in the hand is a good way to get bird flu, you fuckin\' asshole. \n\nGet away from me, go wash your fuckin\' hand!</item>
        <item>Nobody tells me what I can or can\'t eat, \n\nleast of all some guy who\'s job is labelling packets of silica gel.</item>
        <item>We all know that the Swiss are officially neutral. \n\nUnofficially, however, they\'re filthy sons of bitches.</item>
        <item>Remember the old days when \'tweeting\' meant stabbing a hooker?</item>
        <item>I can prove God exists! \n\nIf I could just find that damn receipt from our brunch in heaven…</item>
        <item>We could nip \'March Madness\' in the bud if we watch for the warning signs of \'Brooding Anti-social February Fever\'</item>
        <item>This Lindsay Lohan can\'t swim a stroke but she sure knows every dive in town.</item>
        <item>Call me an old softie, \n\nbut I\'d prefer if you call me a distinguished gentleman with a flagging erection.</item>
        <item>I remember back when the \'Harlem Shake\' was just a black fella holding me upside down off of a fire escape trying to collect his money!</item>
        <item>Deep Throat\' porn legend Harry Reems died. \n\nHow are they going to close that casket?!</item>
        <item>Alfred the Great may well be the greatest monarch in the history of England. \n\nThe worst? Richard the Goat Fucker!</item>
        <item>Hank Williams Jr. called President Obama a Muslim who "hates the US" \n\nIn response, President Obama said, "Why would I hate the US? You guys made me President and I wasn\'t even born here!"</item>
        <item>This Easter Sunday, Snoop Dogg gets to say \n\n"Christ is Rizzisen"</item>
        <item>We wear new clothes on Easter to represent Christ\'s triumphant appearance to the stunned Apostles in a sharp 2-button blazer by Hugo Boss.</item>
        <item>The guy who did the voice of Charlie Brown was arrested for stalking his girlfriend this week. \n\nHe also said the next time Lucy grabs away the football, he\'s going to "cut that bitch".</item>
        <item>Some folks say what this country needs is a good five cent cigar. \n\nI\'m guessing they\'re opposing Obamacare.</item>
        <item>I don\'t know if this counts as an NCAA Cinderella story, \n\nbut one of the Marquette players said he had help making his uniform from a bunch of singing mice and birds.</item>
        <item>Warning to the Easter bunny: \n\nDon\'t put all your eggs in one basket, fella!</item>
        <item>They say the world\'s a smaller place than it used to be, \n\nbut I think that\'s an optical illusion, based on me becoming a big fat guy.</item>
        <item>Growing up, I never would have believed that one day I\'d need a computer just to masturbate.</item>
        <item>Swedish Bond girl Britt Ekland told Piers Morgan this week that she was seduced by Warren Beatty after the legendary lothario took her to an X-rated movie for their first date. \n\nThis is what I have to say about that: "Hey Warren, stop stealing my moves!"</item>
        <item>Thomas Edison invented the lightbulb, \n\nbut I invented the lightbulb up my ass.</item>
        <item>Octomom is facing jail time for committing welfare fraud. \n\nWho didn\'t see that one coming. I mean seriously, a single mother of eight!</item>
        <item>I am not a big fan of videogames where you cannot kill a prostitute.</item>
        <item>I love Lou Gehrig, \n\nbut I\'m not going to stand up in front of a million people and brag that I\'m the luckiest man in the world because some doctors named a disease after me. \n\nConfidence is one thing, but arrogance is the worst disease of them all.</item>
        <item>One day in the hopefully not-too-distant future, North Korean dictator Kim Jong Un is going to hear a loud popping sound. \n\nThe sound of his head coming out of his own ass!</item>
        <item>A Miami Florida pimp is in custody after forcing a 13 year old prostitute to have his name tattooed on her eyelids when she threatened to run away from him. \n\nRoman Thomas III faces charges of human trafficking, false imprisonment, lewd and lascivious exhibition, and delivery of a controlled substance to a child. Y\'know, \n\nI know the scriptures say "judge not lest ye be judged" but I\'m just going to come right out and say it. This \'Roman Thomas III guy\'… this guy\'s a real jerk!</item>
        <item>I used to think revenge was a dish best served cold, \n\nbut then I realized it meant \'getting back at somebody\'.</item>
        <item>Hey, news media, leave Kim Kardashian alone, will you? She\'s pregnant! Of course she\'s going to gain weight, and if anyone knows about rapid weight gain it\'s me. \n\nI went to see the doctor about it and he told me to open my mouth and say OINK!</item>
        <item>I think enough time has passed since 1947 where I can safely admit it. \n\nI wish I was the guy that finally wiped the annoying smirk off the Black Dahlia\'s face.</item>
        <item>Music is the universal language, but one day soon it will be replaced by Chinese.</item>
        <item>Mickey Mantle knew two things, drinking, and playing drunk baseball.</item>
        <item>Why doesn\'t Applebee\'s call their appetizers appletizers? \n\nAnd why doesn\'t that waitress I met at TGI Fridays ever call me back?</item>
        <item>This administration is cutting back drastically on military spending but doesn\'t think defense capabilities will be comprised? \n\nHow so? I\'ll tell you how so! Groupons! Remember Groupons?</item>
        <item>A worldwide scientific study confirms a long held suspicion; \n\nno one anywhere likes drum circles.</item>
        <item>Justin Bieber\'s monkey has been quarantined, \n\nwhich reminds us how far we\'ve come since headlines about Pearl Harbor and D-Day.</item>
        <item>In the coffee shop line today I hear the guy behind me say "I like to start by biting the ears off" \n\nand I had to pray "Please God, let him be talking about a chocolate Easter bunny!"</item>
        <item>Earlier this week Aaron Jackson of Topeka, Kansas painted his house the colors of the gay pride rainbow flag in direct protest of the Westboro Baptist Church. \n\nWhen that didn\'t seem to work, Jackson fucked three of his best buds on his front lawn.</item>
        <item>Chipotle has cancelled its planned sponsorship of the Utah Boy Scout event due to the BSA\'s ban on gay leaders and scouts. \n\nIronic how an all male anti-gay organization would want to put hot thick loads of beef and sour cream in their mouth.</item>
        <item>Former Tennessee Titans cheerleader Elizabeth Leigh Garner, 42 is accused of pulling a 12 year old boy pants off and offering him oral sex. \n\nThe boy refused her advances, \n\nnot because he was 12 but because he was a diehard Colts fan.</item>
        <item>The obituaries are concerning me because people are dying in alphabetical order.</item>
        <item>Former pornstar Jenna Jameson was arrested this weekend after allegedly assaulting someone. \n\nThis may be the most damaging to happen to her image since her 16 year career in pornography.</item>
        <item>Why did the moron throw the clock out the window? \n\nBecause it reminded him of Richard Clock - the man convicted of knife-raping his wife.</item>
        <item>Veterinarians in Colorado have reported that marijuana use is on the rise among dogs. \n\nThey say you will know if your dog is too high if it starts making a really tall sandwich.</item>
        <item>My doctor told me I should start juicing. The problem is I don\'t think he meant ham juice.</item>
        <item>I\'m so fat that when I get my shoes shined I have to take the bootblack\'s word for it!</item>
        <item>Porn actor Ron Jeremy is back at work after having open-heart surgery. \n\nThe name of his next feature is called \'I\'m Going to Have to Sit Down for Most of This\'</item>
        <item>Dance like no one is watching. Sing like no one is listening. Love like you\'ve never been hurt. \n\nAnd fuck like a goddamn retard.</item>
        <item>How many Polish guys does it take to screw in a lightbulb. \n\nThe question can not be answered because Polish people are so fucking stupid that no matter how many of them are available none of them would ever be able to complete that simple task.</item>
        <item>How many comedians does it take to screw in a lightbulb? \n\nTwo. \n\nOne to do it, and the other to go "How long\'s he been up there?"</item>
        <item>Have you heard about the four NFL players that are coming out of the closet? \n\nIt\'s about time I think. I think it\'s high time. \n\nBecause isn\'t it strange that nobody\'s come out of closet in the entire sport of football? Where there\'s 2000+ players? So there\'s a great deal of speculation on who those four openly gay players will be. Nobody knows. My guess is it\'s those four that are always sucking each others cocks.</item>
        <item>Because of droughts all over Europe, scientists are predicting a global shortage of olive oil. \n\nSoon the world will know how Popeye felt after the death of his wife.</item>
        <item>It takes forever to get a pilot\'s license, \n\nbut it only takes a couple of minutes to steal a pilot\'s jacket and hat.</item>
        <item>Barbara Walters is planning to announce her retirement, \n\nwhat\'s next for Babs? \n\nDeath.</item>
        <item>I think there\'s nothing cooler than being a lone wolf. \n\nExcept at wolf-picnics when you don\'t have a partner for the wolf-wheelbarrow races.</item>
        <item>Call me crazy, but I take orders from Martians who send secret messages beamed out from the antenna at the top of the Empire State Building.</item>
        <item>A Georgia high school is planning to merge their formerly all black and all white proms into a single event. \n\nThe theme of this June\'s dance? \'An Evening of Unbridled Race War\'</item>
        <item>A Florida man was arrested for stealing a truck filled with $76,000 worth of Campbell\'s soup. \n\nI, for one, hope this guy goes away for \'Mmm, mmm, good!\'</item>
        <item>My girlfriend and I have a deal where we have one celebrity that we can sleep with and it\'s not considered cheating. \n\nMine is that woman who plays Madea.</item>
        <item>In Kansas, a gay-rights activist named Aaron Jackson paid $83,000 to buy a house across from the homophobic Westboro Baptist Church and had it painted rainbow colours. \n\nMr. Jackson plans to recoup his investment by… \n\nwell, actually there\'s no plan. \n\nHave fun living in a hideous house in Kansas across from some vicious bigots!</item>
        <item>Its Earth Day! The one day of the year where you can jerk off outside and nothing bad can happen! \n\n(I don\'t know what Earth Day is)</item>
        <item>A new study shows that most men can identify a gay man by his face alone. \n\nIt\'s the face that\'s buried in another man\'s asshole.</item>
        <item>Apparently someone in Germany stole 5 metric tons of Nutella. \n\nPolice haven\'t arrested anyone yet but they are questioning Günther Hasbargen, the 700 pound man that smells like chocolate and hazelnuts who guards the Nutella storage facility.</item>
        <item>I love the movie \'42\'. \n\nIt\'s Chadwick Boseman like you\'ve never seen him before!</item>
        <item>There\'s no wrong way to eat a Reese\'s… \n\nsays the guy who didn\'t shove a bunch of Reese\'s up his ass.</item>
        <item>Amanda Bynes is a lush blonde who\'s quickly turning into a blonde lush.</item>
        <item>College freshman Scott Damerow set a new world record by using his head to bust 142 eggs and he now officially holds a place in the Guinness Book of Fucking Retards.</item>
        <item>If you were a Russian prostitute on a date with serial killer Andrei Chikatilo aka. The Rostov Ripper and he couldn\'t achieve an erection… \n\nthat was not your lucky day.</item>
        <item>The Al Qaeda online magazine \'Inspire\' has a recipe for a homemade bomb. \n\nThey also have a recipe for a pretty darn good peach cobbler.</item>
        <item>You know my clothes make me look slimmer. \n\nBut they did not fool that flight of stairs that collapsed under my astonishing new girth.</item>
        <item>I loved Liberace but with all due respect, man, \n\nif you kicked that guy in the ass a hundred cocks would fall out.</item>
        <item>Fast and Furious 6 opens next week. The cast is getting a little older, \n\nit\'s less \'Fast and Furious\' and more \'Brisk and Peeved\'</item>
        <item>A good name for a dog is \'Syndrome\'. \n\nThen when he tries to attack someone you can yell "Down Syndrome!"</item>
        <item>I\'ve never gotten a decent explanation as to how Popeye the Sailor Man lost his eye.</item>
        <item>ZZ Top sang that every girl\'s crazy \'bout a sharp dressed man. \n\nBut you know what they\'re not crazy about? Gross long beards.</item>
        <item>Movie star and award-winning director Ben Affleck has vowed to live for one day on $1.50 or as Adam Eget calls it "a raise".</item>
        <item>In England a woman was arrested for throwing a birthday party for her 16 year old son that involved marijuana, alcohol and strippers. \n\nNow she\'s got an even bigger problem: What to do for his 17th birthday.</item>
        <item>Horses must love that they\'re the go-to animals when saying a guy has a huge cock. \n\nI bet giraffes have huge cocks, I\'m sure of it. \n\nBut let\'s face it, no one\'s ever going to say "That guy\'s hung like a giraffe" unless his cock is yellow and has brown spots on it. In which case who cares how big his fucking cock is, he has weeks to live.</item>
        <item>Tomorrow is National Secretary\'s Day. \n\nI plan on getting my secretary the same thing I always do. A big fat goosing!</item>
        <item>Remember the good old days back when MILF stood for Mentally Ill Ladies I\'d like to Fuck?</item>
        <item>There\'s going to be a broadway musical based on the movie, \'Rocky\'. \n\nIn the broadway musical version, after Rocky climbs the steps of the art museum he goes inside and spends 2 hours looking at paintings.</item>
        <item>Tim Tebow\'s time in New York wasn\'t a total loss, \n\nhe had a monument built to him in Central Park. A bench.</item>
        <item>Catherine Zeta-Jones has been diagnosed with bipolar disorder. \n\nHalf the time she\'s Zeta, half the time she\'s Jones.</item>
        <item>A new tabloid rumor: 205 pound Kim Kardashian might be getting paid to gain weight by some weight-loss program or reality show that will then get her to lose weight. \n\nI have a similar deal, only I paid them, and by them I mean Zankou Chicken. \n\nAnd in exchange they give me some Zankou Chicken.</item>
        <item>Cats and paraplegics have a lot in common. \n\nFor starters, neither appreciates being tossed into your neighbour\'s pool.</item>
        <item>They say there\'s no people like show people, \n\nbut now scientists have found that show people are genetically linked to the Laplanders and the Finns.</item>
        <item>Despite all the advances in veterinary medicine and racing technology the Kentucky Derby record set by Secretariat still stands, \n\nthe reason? \n\nToday\'s horses are total pussies.</item>
        <item>Catherine Zeta-Jones admitted she is bi-polar. \n\nHalf the time she\'s deliriously happy, \n\nand the other half she has to suck an old man\'s cock.</item>
        <item>If tampons are called sanitary napkins, \n\nhow unsanitary must regular napkins be?</item>
        <item>Scientists have found a submerged mass of granite off the coast of South America that they are calling the \'Brazilian Atlantis\'. \n\nDammit, I want to be called the \'Brazilian Atlantis\'!</item>
        <item>Crews in Ohio dismantled a tavern wall in search of Jimmy Hoffa\'s body, and sure enough, they found the inside of a tavern wall!</item>
        <item>I once missed a day of cosmetology school and later I had to take a make-up class.</item>
        <item>The Dalai Lama said that "killing in the name of religion is unthinkable". \n\nHey, thanks Dalai Lama! I\'m sure everybody will fucking listen to you!</item>
        <item>Yesterday was \'bring-your-daughter-to-work day\', which was awkward for Adam Eget. \n\nDo you know how hard it is to fuck a whore with her kid on the edge of the bed playing Nintendo?</item>
        <item>I like hotels, they make your bed, make your dinner, send housekeepers up to watch you masturbate, its a dream.</item>
        <item>The parents of Honey Boo-Boo are getting married this week. \n\nI don\'t know what any of that means but it sounds fucking retarded.</item>
        <item>Recent studies show fish can communicate with each other using subtle physical gestures. \n\nOne of their most common messages: (make a subtle gesture) "Lets leave this party early"</item>
        <item>I assume anyone smiling is on meth.</item>
        <item>According to a new survey, Robin Roberts is America\'s most trusted news anchor. \n\nAnd America\'s least trusted news anchor? Matt Liar!</item>
        <item>Ariel Castro the Cleveland kidnapper and rapist must have had a very difficult upbringing. \n\nHis last name\'s the same as a ruthless dictator, and his first name\'s the same as an adorable little red-haired mermaid.</item>
        <item>If you guys think it\'s weird that that guy in Cleveland kept three women in his basement as sex slaves, \n\nwait \'til you hear what my middle-aged Uncle Gordon kept in his basement… \n\nA fuckin\' electric train!</item>
        <item>A Florida university student was caught streaking on campus and apparently told police he was on acid, and asked them to cut his dick off. \n\nBoy, these kids today are crazy, back in my day we didn\'t need drugs, we would just cut our own dicks off.</item>
        <item>There\'s a new 3D version of the Great Gatsby coming out. \n\nIn 3D, it was almost like the sober examination of the unrestrained materialism and absent moral center of the roaring twenties jumps right out at you!</item>
        <item>I think my doctor might be retarded. \n\nWhy? His name is Doctor Retardo.</item>
        <item>42 year old Richard Swanson set out to dribble a soccer ball from Seattle to Brazil, but got hit by a car in Oregon and died. \n\nWell at least he got to die doing what he loved. Dribbling a soccer ball in traffic.</item>
        <item>Pain and Gain the new movie directed by Michael Bay. \n\nReviewers are calling it everything from "shit" to "fucking shit"!</item>
        <item>My landlord managed to get rid of 230 pounds of ugly fat - he evicted me!</item>
        <item>Sure we all know about Norm\'s astonishing weight gain - but i think it\'s become a bit wearisome. \n\nSo let\'s agree to stop having fun at his expanse.</item>
        <item>Four of the top 5 picks in the NFL draft were offensive tackles \n\nwhich is a great thing to tell your wife as the love drains from her eyes.</item>
        <item>Danny Devito looks like one of those guys with a short but thick penis.</item>
        <item>You know dogs and humans love to run because apparently it gives them a natural high, similar to marijuana, according to the university of Arizona. \n\nAfter running, what are called cannabinoids, the chemical found in marijuana that gives you the feeling of euphoria, are higher in humans and dogs, and this encourages them to run again… \n\nto 7/11 for a slurpee!</item>
        <item>A man in Taiwan reportedly cut off his own penis to win an argument with his wife. \n\nThat reminds me of that episode of "Everybody Loves Raymond" where Raymond forgot Debra\'s birthday and had to cut his own cock off.</item>
        <item>Before I begin I have a quick public service announcement. \n\nWould somebody, anybody, please fuck Martha Stewart?</item>
        <item>For the 9th consecutive year, JetBlue Airlines ranked 1st for satisfaction among all North American airlines. \n\nY\'know which ranked least in satisfaction? 9/11 Airlines.</item>
        <item>I can understand why Barbara Walters is retiring. \n\nIt must be exhausting occasionally appearing on \'The View\'.</item>
        <item>Engaging in hate speech is wrong and terrible and should never be tolerated. \n\nBut you have to admit, engaging in a hate stutter would be kind of cute.</item>
        <item>A \'Papa John\'s\' delivery man has been arrested for allegedly selling more than $40,000 in cocaine hidden in pizza boxes, to undercover police officers. \n\nThis raises an important question: Wheres all that pizza that was supposed to go in those boxes? And can I have them to eat?</item>
        <item>Sesame Street introduced its very first Latino character, Armando. \n\nBut it\'s not going great, apparently on the first day he got into a knife fight and stabbed the letter A.</item>
        <item>The FDA is investigating health risks posed by Wrigley\'s new caffeinated gum. \n\nWhere the hell was the FDA when York Peppermint Patties were making people shiver and have involuntary orgasms?</item>
        <item>Time Magazine named the Top 100 Most Influential People in the World. \n\nThe Top 100 included Justin Timberlake, Beyoncé, Jimmy Kimmel… \n\nin your FACE, Ueli Maurer, President of the Swiss Confederation!</item>
        <item>Nowadays most teenagers don\'t watch their favorite shows on actual TV sets. \n\nInstead they just blow each other.</item>
        <item>How many people have to die before we finally do something about dropping pianos?!</item>
        <item>The latest Archie Comic shows gay character Kevin kissing his boyfriend Devin. \n\nAnother barrier will be broken next month when in a dream sequence, Jughead will be shown fisting Betty Crocker.</item>
        <item>Barbara Walters announced that she\'s retiring from \'The View\'. \n\nWell actually she announced it five years ago, but nobody could hear her over those yammering bitches.</item>
        <item>They say pimpin\' ain\'t easy… \n\nbut what they won\'t tell you is it\'s much, much more difficult being a prostitute.</item>
        <item>It\'s hard to believe that the entire cast of Saved by the Bell is now dead.</item>
        <item>George Clooney may be a dapper fellow, \n\nbut don\'t forget, he whacks off just like the rest of us.</item>
        <item>If there\'s two things I\'m 100% sure are true, \n\nit\'s that 1) No means no. 2) You should never take no for an answer.</item>
        <item>There is a new service called \'Sidecar\', where if you need a ride somewhere you will be picked up by a stranger and driven to your location. \n\nHowever in a few months the company plans on going back to its original name: \'Murder\'</item>
        <item>Accomplished comedian Sinbad has announced he\'s filing for bankruptcy for the 2nd time. \n\nSounds like things have gone from Sin-bad, to Sin-worse.</item>
        <item>A lot of people talk about masturbating to the Sears catalogue when they were younger. \n\nBut I\'m a lot older than that, back in my day you actually had to go to a Sears store and fucking whack off!</item>
        <item>Organist Ray Manzarek died this week at age 74… \n\nTHE CURSE OF THE DOORS</item>
        <item>My Aunt turned her house into a bed &amp; breakfast. \n\nI guess she woke up and said "not enough strangers are fucking here"</item>
        <item>Whenever someone says "I have a couple irons in the fire" \n\nI think, "is one of them a job writing blacksmithing metaphors</item>
        <item>If the Miami Heat win the NBA championship this year, I\'m going to eat my hat. \n\nIt\'s not that I care or think that they\'re going to win, it\'s just that I want to eat my hat.</item>
        <item>This year\'s most popular iPhone game is \'Clash of the Clans\' \n\nThe least popular iPhone game? \'Cut my Cock Off\'</item>
        <item>Today is the 11th birthday of President Obama\'s youngest daughter Sasha. \n\nOr as I like to call her, \'the uppity one\'</item>
        <item>Well we\'re now into those hazy crazy lazy days of summer. \n\nEspecially those of us who are over-medicated schizophrenics who live near smoky industrial parks.</item>
        <item>I think there\'s some trouble over at Craigslist. \n\nI went over there and saw an ad: \'Someone to kill Craig\'s wife\'</item>
        <item>You know that sweet old song \'Tea for Two\'? Nobody near us to see us or hear us? \n\nI think those people wanted to get down to some serious fucking.</item>
        <item>I think the reason I most look forward to China ruling the earth is that all of their last names sound like slang for \'cock\'.</item>
        <item>Astronomers have discovered three new planets that have an atmosphere conducive to human life. \n\nAnd they\'ve discovered one that has an "atmo" conducive to hipster life.</item>
        <item>Michael Douglas portrayed the flamboyant entertainer Liberace in the new HBO film \'Behind the Candelabra\'. \n\nI\'d like to say something to Michael Douglas: I sang with Liberace, I knew Liberace, Liberace was a friend of mine. Michael Douglas, you\'re no Liberace!</item>
        <item>Why is it so difficult to find pornography about people in stable monogamous relationships?</item>
        <item>China\'s government has reported that they have lost over 28,000 rivers in the past decade. \n\nMy theory is they sold it into the sordid world of underground river sex trafficking.</item>
        <item>A man in France tried to rob a bank using underwear as a mask, \n\nthe cops put him in jail right after a quick debriefing.</item>
        <item>You know, I\'m old enough to remember back to simpler, more innocent times, \n\nwhen the worst thing you\'d hear about on the news was hijacked jet liners flying into buildings.</item>
        <item>The world\'s 2nd oldest man died this week at 113. Good news for the world\'s 3rd oldest man who also got bad news this week: He\'s dying.</item>
        <item>Scientists now say that trout can communicate with each other with subtle physical gestures. \n\nWow. Just when you thought trout couldn\'t get any more fascinating.</item>
        <item>Mondays aren\'t actually worse than any other day according to a group of researchers who\'ve never read a Garfield comic.</item>
        <item>Archaeologists excavating a trash pit at the Jamestown Colony site in Virginia have found direct evidence of human cannibalism. \n\nIt\'s believed to be the first historical occurrence of someone eating a bag of dicks.</item>
        <item>Two women accused of using sorcery have been beheaded in a remote village in Papua New Guinea. \n\nA team of police rushed to the scene but were forced to stand by and watch the victims being decapitated by axes as locals refused to let them come to their aid. \n\nIf you ever go to a remote village in Papua New Guinea, at all costs avoid using sorcery!</item>
        <item>A Las Vegas woman was arrested after hiding a stolen Rolex in her vagina. \n\nWow, now Bruce Jenner\'s just gone too far.</item>
        <item>Bill Clinton says he wouldn\'t be surprised if some day we are visited by aliens from outer space. \n\nDemocratic presidential hopeful Hillary Clinton said: "Shouldn\'t you be getting a blowjob somewhere?"</item>
        <item>Health officials in Texas raided the home of 60 year old sisters and found over 100 cats. \n\nThe cats are named Bootsy, Lola, Tippy, Cornelia, Fluffy, Minerva, Ringo, Jasper, Charlie, Spanky, Snooks, Doodle, Wally Happy-pants, Zeke, Veronica, Dolly, Clyde, Ajax, Rusty, Puff-ball, Snuffy, Sylvia, Mr. Moody, Leonardo, Zeke, Tawana, Evinrude, Nimrod, Sylvester, Skee-ball, Toots, Jupiter, Lady Agatha, Murgatroyd, Lula-belle, Newton, Felix, Smurfette…</item>
        <item>The street drug \'Special K\' has been found to be an excellent treatment for depression. \n\nThis according to the New England Journal of Gary Busey.</item>
        <item>Michigan man Curtis Peterson received a 15 year prison sentence for having sex with his pet pitbull. \n\nWhat\'s that lassie? Woof woof? Grandma got stuck in a well? Woof woof? Oh, you got raped?</item>
        <item>Self-described Canadian porn star Luka Rocco Magnotta, heading to court soon for the grisly murder of his Chinese boyfriend. \n\nMagnotta allegedly killed Lin Jun on video tape. He started by cutting Jun\'s penis off, leading to his lover bleeding out live on video tape. Magnotta then went to his kitchen and placed his boyfriend\'s penis into a skillet frying it until it was golden brown. While taking his last breath, Jun witnessed his supposed soulmate feast on his genitals. After he had perished, Magnotta began dismembering him, sending packages of his - \n\nI mean this guy was a real jerk!</item>
        <item>A study has found that the average high school prom go-er now spends $1000. \n\nOr $2000 if you count the abortion.</item>
        <item>A Westchester parking enforcement officer stole $89,000 in quarters. \n\nHow much laundry does this guy need to do?</item>
        <item>The man behind the voice of Tony the Tiger died at 64. \n\nHis last words? \n\nI don\'t feel Grrrrrr-eaaaat!</item>
        <item>Two strangers were arrested for having sex on a plane. How about that? \n\nYou know who I feel sorry for? \n\nThe guy in the middle seat.</item>
        <item>Neil Patrick Harris posed nude for the cover of Rolling Stone except for a hat hanging off his weiner. \n\nAnd this morning Adam Eget woke up and said "Hey where\'s my hat?"</item>
        <item>Dr. Dre announced that he\'s the first hip-hop billionaire, \n\na regular J. Paul Ghetto!</item>
        <item>All the charities that Donald Sterling donated millions of dollars to are giving it back to him. \n\nWell, that\'ll show him.</item>
        <item>To stop a pitbull attacking his daughter a Texas man bit the dog. \n\nThat\'s an interesting story, but it\'s not what I would call news.</item>
        <item>The search continues for the missing Malaysian airliner. \n\nIn related news a plane was spotted by some cavemen in the year 365BC.</item>
        <item>A man in Chipata, Zambia allowed a hyena to eat his penis after being told by a witch doctor it would help him to become rich. \n\nIs it me or does it sound like that hyena and witch doctor were in cahoots?</item>
        <item>tractor-trailer flipped over releasing millions of bees, which stung the driver hundreds of times. \n\nSpeaking from the hospital, the driver said: No flowers?</item>
        <item>I realized in therapy that I\'m not afraid of dying, \n\nI\'m afraid of living. \n\nOh no, I\'m afraid of dying!</item>
        <item>A penny earned is nothing to brag about.</item>
        <item>Police in Tennessee arrested a teenage girl when they found a loaded gun in her vagina. \n\nWhen questioned, the boyfriend said "I guess that explains why my cock kept getting blown off"</item>
        <item>A 28 year old med student is auctioning off her virginity online. \n\nFor three hundred thousand dollars you can have the worst sex of your life!</item>
        <item>George Clooney is engaged. \n\nThe rich and handsome 53 year old told reporters "It\'s time for me to settle down and start officially cheating on a heartsick and disillusioned spouse."</item>
        <item>Now I don\'t know much about geopolitics, \n\nbut that is one cool name for a country: \'Chad\'.</item>
        <item>Kidnapped schoolgirls in Nigeria are being forced to marry their captors. \n\nI\'m glad to hear these kidnappers are old-fashioned.</item>
        <item>Some of the 200 Nigerian schoolgirls kidnapped by extremists in Nigeria have been forced to marry their kidnappers. \n\nWorse than that, they\'ve been forced to laugh at their husband\'s stories even after hearing them for the umpteenth time.</item>
        <item>If I had a gun to my head and had to pick a vice presidential candidate to have sex with, I would choose Sarah Palin. \n\nAnd Spiro Agnew.</item>
        <item>Malaysian Flight 370 is still missing. \n\nYou know where they\'re going to find it? The last place they look!</item>
        <item>Yo momma\'s so fat she developed type-2 diabetes and congestive heart failure! Snap!</item>
        <item>If thinking that women are not funny, emotionally irrational, and less intelligent than men makes me sexist, \n\nthen yes, I am sexist!</item>
        <item>Here\'s what I\'ve learned: \n\nYou beat up and toss one 19 year old Hispanic hooker out a window and they never let you forget it!</item>
        <item>Have you ever seen these adult films that feature only men? \n\nThey\'re awful!</item>
        <item>It was announced this week that the Archie Comic Books will kill off the character Archie in July. \n\nThis is disappointing because if there\'s one Archie character that should die, it\'s that cock sucker Jughead.</item>
        <item>Al Sharpton said that the FBI hired him to spy on the mob in the 1970\'s, \n\nbecause if there\'s one thing the mob trusts, it\'s loud black guys.</item>
        <item>When I die I want my body donated to science. \n\nBut more specifically, a scientist who is working on bringing dead guys back to life.</item>
        <item>Two businessmen bought the Milwaukee Bucks for 550 million dollars. \n\nThey are very excited with their purchase, as this is the only legal way to own black people.</item>
        <item>Chicago is now #1 in murder and sausages. \n\nThat sounds like my kind of town!</item>
        <item>The World Cup has arrived! \n\nSo, if you\'re wondering why your local bar smells, it\'s because of all the dirty foreigners.</item>
        <item>This week I learned that just because I masturbated to that picture of a guy falling to his death on 9/11, \n\ndoesn\'t mean I have to share it.</item>
        <item>Brides magazine released a list of \'11 Ways to be a Terrible Bride\'. \n\nThey include: Don\'t Interfere with the Wedding Planner \n\nDon\'t Lie About How Much the Wedding Cost Your Family \n\nand coming in at #1: Don\'t Fuck Your Husband\'s Best Friends</item>
        <item>Harriette Thompson, 91 finished running the Rock\'n\'Roll Marathon in San Diego in just over 7 hours, becoming the oldest person to complete a marathon, and setting a world record for the fastest time in her age group. \n\nThe previous record was set by Mildred Kennelworth who died during mile 1.</item>
        <item>Kim and Kanye celebrated their daughter North West\'s one year birthday by throwing a big party with jugglers, a bouncy house and a ferris wheel. \n\nThe bad news is that North West is a baby and it doesn\'t know what the fuck is going on.</item>
        <item>A study has found that men are just as likely as women to spread gossip. \n\nAt least that\'s what I heard Rick tell Brad, who by the way has a crush on Patty.</item>
        <item>Hey Madonna says she\'s planning to remake the movie \'Casablanca\'. \n\nFinally! Someone is going to get it right!</item>
        <item>Here\'s a really easy way to figure out if you\'re taking too many meds: \n\nYou refer to your medication as \'meds\'.</item>
        <item>The only things certain in life are death, taxes, and getting caught whacking off in a Target dressing room.</item>
        <item>Hey, you\'re not going to believe this, \n\nbut Bill Maher is giving away the solution to all our problems… \n\nfor free!</item>
        <item>Know who\'s even crazier than cat ladies? \n\nSnake ladies!</item>
        <item>Workers at a Harvard University library have discovered a book that\'s bound with human skin. \n\nThey were able to determine the part of the body that the skin came from after it was grabbed by a sexy librarian and immediately expanded to 3 times its size.</item>
        <item>When Gwyneth Paltrow says that being a movie star is harder than working a 9–5 job, \n\nshe knows, because she spent years clearing heavy debris from demolition sites - \n\noh no, wait - this just in - Gwyneth Paltrow has never done shit!</item>
        <item>I\'m the Ray Allen of my local Applebees because I\'m always nailing 3s.</item>
        <item>Alex Trebek set a Guinness world record for most game shows hosted. \n\nThe previous record was: Who gives a fuck?</item>
        <item>Three children were injured when a cannon exploded during a Civil War re-enactment. \n\nTo keep things authentic, the children had their limbs sawed off with rusty hacksaws.</item>
        <item>President Obama in a speech this past week said that we should solve the nation\'s bee problem. \n\nOh, God, we elected a guy who sympathizes with BEES?</item>
        <item>Presidential Fact: \n\nBarack Obama is the first president to ever say the \'N\' word as a term of endearment.</item>
        <item>A 89 year old Washington man fought off a robber with a golf club, \n\nthough to be fair, the only reason the guy was swinging a golf club was because he mistook the robber for the grim spectre of death.</item>
        <item>A Pakistani father stoned his daughter to death for marrying a man of her own choosing. \n\nWhich means Pakistan\'s tourism board is going to have to come up with a new slogan to replace \n\n"Come to Pakistan! Three whole days without anyone being brutally stoned to death by their own Father!"</item>
        <item>It\'s kind of a weird feeling watching the Flintstones lately, with their stone-age drive-in movies, and their caveman bowling… \n\nit just seems so dated!</item>
        <item>A cowboy at a rodeo in Georgia used his lasso to apprehend a gunman. \n\nAt least, that\'s according to a recent segment of America\'s hottest new game show: \'Georgia Police Blotter or Episode Synopsis from Walker Texas Ranger?\'</item>
        <item>An Orlando police officer\'s press conference on curbing gun violence was interrupted by gun shots. \n\nWitnesses say the shots were incredibly loud, though not as loud as the deafening irony.</item>
        <item>All My Children star Matthew Cowles has died at the age of 69. Or has he?</item>
        <item>Research shows the obesity epidemic is primarily affecting lower income Americans. \n\nNo lower income Americans could be reached for comment because they were busy waddling around Six Flags, gnawing on a giant turkey leg, and waiting in line to buy an airbrushed Yosemite Sam tank top.</item>
        <item>Miss Nevada has been crowned the new Miss USA. \n\nI must now apologize to Miss Delaware. \n\nI actually have nothing to do with the final decision but I will treasure our evening together forever.</item>
        <item>John Kerry said that the latest terrorist threats against America are "baloney". \n\nThen he went on to shout "Why don\'t you pussies put your money where your mouth is?!"</item>
        <item>Secretary of State John Kerry calls the latest terror threats to America "Baloney". \n\nOn his lunch-meat danger scale that\'s more dangerous than salami, but not as dangerous as turkey loaf.</item>
        <item>The world\'s oldest man, an 111 year old parapsychologist has passed away. \n\nHe now knows for sure that all that stuff that he believed in was bullshit.</item>
        <item>The world\'s oldest man, Alexander Imich, passed away at 111. \n\nAnd the world\'s youngest man, Declan McAlistair was just born. Oh wait! Correction - the world\'s youngest man Fan Woo Chung was just born- Wait, no, it\'s Gaston LeClaire- No! Javier Guitierez- No! It\'s Takeo Yamashita- No! It\'s… \n\nno wonder they don\'t keep track of the world\'s youngest man.</item>
        <item>A list of the world\'s top 25 amusement parks was released this week with Disney\'s Magic Kingdom coming in at #1. \n\nNot making the list: Kyle\'s Rape Dungeon.</item>
        <item>This week I learned you can pay your dentist with blowjobs.</item>
        <item>I do a terrible John Travolta impression \n\nbut I find the impression gets a lot better when my male masseuse is jerking me off.</item>
        <item>You know they had a big Black Mass devil worship this week. \n\nBut I skipped it because I believe you can be just as close to Satan on a golf course as in some stuffy old Satanic Church.</item>
        <item>Some Biblical scholars now believe that Jesus Christ was married. \n\nThey also believe he had the world\'s worst bachelor party.</item>
        <item>A Chinese man spent 10 years developing a suitcase that doubles as a motorized scooter. \n\nThere\'s no word on whether he had any particular hopes or dreams.</item>
        <item>Movie fans are now celebrating the 30th anniversary of Ghostbusters and are demanding a Ghostbusters 3. \n\nAt least, according to a homeless dude on my block, who looks suspiciously like Ernie Hudson.</item>
        <item>In Alabama, a Youth Ministry group is under fire for putting up a billboard that quotes Adolf Hitler. \n\nTo be fair, they did pick his most inspirational quote.</item>
        <item>That \'Weird Al\' Yankovic ain\'t so weird. He just sings parody songs. \n\nMy friend \'Weird Phil\', that guy\'s weird, he saves all his cum in Sparklets bottles for marriage.</item>
        <item>The world\'s oldest man died yesterday. \n\nCause of death: Everybody yelled "Surprise!"</item>
        <item>In World Cup soccer, Mexico defeated Cameroon one to nothing. \n\nOr as it\'s known in soccer, a blowout.</item>
        <item>Jonah Hill says his heart is broken over the fact he was caught on camera calling a photographer a gay slur. \n\nAnd speaking of things that are broken: Jonah Hill\'s chair.</item>
        <item>I had an uncle, mean guy, he was a prize fighter. \n\nHe once broke both of his hands in a fight against a washer-dryer he won on \'The Price is Right\'.</item>
        <item>When I was a child my parents told me my uncle was \'sleeping with the fishes\' which at the time I assumed meant that he bought a waterbed… \n\nbut then I found out he had been killed and his body buried at sea.</item>
        <item>My father was recently diagnosed with shingles which is a terrible sickness that usually only affects roofs.</item>
        <item>Hotel Rwanda has a great score on Rotten Tomatoes but their Yelp reviews are terrible.</item>
        <item>Growing up I had a dog with an eating disorder, \n\nhe wouldn\'t eat my homework.</item>
        <item>A young Zika mosquito went out flying for the first time, when he came back his father asked \'How was it?\' \n\nThe young mosquito replied \'Great, everyone was clapping for me!\'</item>
        <item>Hillary has the support of the Orlando terrorist\'s Dad, Trump has the support of white supremacist groups. \n\nI can\'t decide who I support until the Zika virus weighs in.</item>
        <item tools:ignore="Typos">Playboy magazine has done away with the nude photo layouts altogether. \n\nIn other words they\'ve eliminated ladies in the altogether altogether!</item>
        <item>How come the term \'adult toy\' always refers to something you can shove up your asshole and never like a big racecar?</item>
        <item>Scientists have discovered a vegan spider in South Africa that will not eat ants. \n\nIt refuses to eat ants even if it\'s starving but it will eat tofu shaped like ants.</item>
        <item>Researchers in Bermuda believe that they may have finally solved the mystery of Amelia Earhart\'s disappearance: \n\nShe was a bad pilot.</item>
        <item>The Deer Hunter is a terrific movie unless you shelled out three bucks to see some actual deer hunting.</item>
        <item>Say what you will about Elon Musk but with his new plan to bring people to Mars, \n\nnobody is a more creative serial killer.</item>
        <item>You know the funniest part about doing an office conga line? \n\nWhen you look back and realise you\'re doing it alone and you\'re not in an office, you\'re in a psychiatric hospital.</item>
        <item>I heard that when Beethoven was 16 he wrote his first symphony. \n\nThis is the kinda guy who makes you realise what an utter sham your life has been. \n\nWhen I was 16, I was in a McDonald\'s saying "You want lids on these?"</item>
        <item>A surname you don\'t hear much anymore? \n\nFlintstone.</item>
        <item>I played a great club here in the city, \'Catch a Rising Star\', \n\nboy, that\'s a good club, but across the street they have a tough club, have you been there? \'Snub a Bombing Has-been\'</item>
        <item>Here\'s something you should never say in bed: \n\n\'That oughta hold you for a while, Gertrude!\'</item>
        <item>I thought I was going to be rich, but it turns out there isn\'t much call for radish cider.</item>
        <item>Researchers have discovered that cockroaches have personalities. \n\nNot great ones, mind you.</item>
        <item>Why is taking no pleasure in things I used to enjoy a sign of depression? \n\nMaybe I\'m just finally sick of crayoning!</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>